https://www.newpig.com/privacypolicy

Password
Forgot password?
Reset
First time here? Register now.
Search
Free Ceramic Mug with Coaster Lid with a $199 order. Promo code PIGMUGLID.
Workplace Safety
Personal Safety (PPE)
Shop By Regulation
EPA's SPCC: Active vs. Passive Containment for Oil Spill Prevention
EPA's Resource Conservation & Recovery Act (RCRA) Waste Management Program
EPA's Stormwater Pollution Prevention Plan (SWPPP) Requirements
EPA's Closed Container & Secondary Containment for Haz Waste
Quick Order
Know your item #? Order faster!
Please enter an item number.
New Pig Privacy Policy
New Pig Corporation (“New Pig,” “us,” “we” or “our”) owns and operates the newpig.com website ("Site") and customer service telephone line at 1-800-HOT-HOGS (1-800-468-4647). This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how New Pig collects, uses, shares and stores your information when you use this Site, do business with us over the telephone, place orders using our Pigalog catalog, send us emails or faxes, interact with us through social media, provide information through electronic data interchange (“EDI”), or through any other interactions you may have with New Pig at tradeshows, conventions and elsewhere (collectively, the “Services”). This Policy also explains how you can exercise certain rights you may have in connection with your privacy and personal information.
This Policy is effective as of: December 18, 2019.
For ease of reference, you may click on any of the following links to jump to one of the sections addressed below:
1.
Scope of this Policy
2.
Modifications
3.
Information We Collect, Use and Share
4.
Disclosure or Sale of Personal Information
5.
Your Rights and Choices
6.
Securing Personal Information
7.
Children's Policy
8.
Non-U.S. Concerns
9.
Terms of Use
10. Contacting New Pig Corporation
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Policy covers only the Services identified above, and does not apply to information which you may send us by other means. Other New Pig sites, locations and services, whether online or offline, may have their own privacy policies, and you should consult those accordingly.
If you are within or are a resident of a member nation of the EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA (the “EEA,” which includes the 27 European Union Member States, Iceland, Lichtenstein and Norway), Switzerland or the United Kingdom (“UK”) (collectively, the “EU”), you are not authorized to use these Services. Instead, please visit the New Pig Europe website at https://www.newpig.eu, and click here to learn about how we collect, use, share and secure your personal data, and how you can exercise your privacy rights.
This Site contains links to external sites, including those embedded in third-party advertisements or sponsor information, that are not controlled by New Pig. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and data collection policies for such third-party sites. You should consult the privacy policies of those sites for details.
^Top
Modifications
New Pig reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time. Since this Policy may change as we modify or expand our Services, we suggest that you check back from time to time in order to understand how we treat your information. Our Policy’s effective date will always be set forth at the beginning and end of the Policy. Any changes will be immediately incorporated into this Policy, and will be prospective only. We will not make any changes that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so.
Any change to this Policy is effective immediately. Your continued use of the Services after any changes are made to this Policy constitutes your acceptance of the changes. If any changes are unacceptable to you, you should cease all use of the Services.
^Top
Information We Collect, Use and Share
Personal information is generally defined as information that, by itself or in combination with other information, identifies, relates to, describes, references, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer, device or household (“Personal Information”). Personal Information can include, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, email address, username and password, IP address or other online identifiers, browsing or search history, credit/debit card number or other financial information, professional or employment-related information, office address and other business information, demographic information, consumer preferences, biometric information such as fingerprints, precise location information, or any other type of information that, directly or indirectly, can be linked to or is reasonably capable of being associated with you.
When using New Pig’s Services, we may collect, use and share the following categories of Personal Information from you in the following ways:
Categories of Personal Information we collect
We may collect this Personal Information when you…
We collect this Personal Information so that we may…
Types of third parties that may receive this Personal Information
Contact information and other data that could be used to identify or communicate with you, including your name, alias, signature, mailing/shipping address, email address, telephone number, fax number, company name, job title, role or other professional or business information, and any inferences we might draw from such information.
•	Create an account with us;
•	Register for a webinar;
•	Submit a request for information on goods or services offered on or through the Services;
•	Sign up to receive mailings, newsletters, e-mail updates or other communications about New Pig products and services which may be of interest to you;
•	Request a Pigalog catalog;
•	Order and pay for New Pig products and services;
•	Submit routing requests for custom shipping;
•	Contact New Pig with questions or comments;
•	Participate in a promotion, contest or survey;
•	Supply it to customer lead generation providers;
•	Interact with us at tradeshows and conferences;
•	Allow us to visit your business; or
•	Provide it to us in the content of any communications you direct to New Pig.
•	Administer your account;
•	Process and respond to your requests for information;
•	Process payment information when you order a New Pig product or service;
•	Communicate with you regarding the status of your order;
•	Send you products and anything else you order for shipping;
•	Respond to your questions and comments;
•	Provide you with information on new products, services, promotions and other updates in which we think you may be interested;
•	Shipping and mail providers including storage facilities and dropshippers;
•	Payment processors;
•	Marketing firms including email marketing vendors;
•	Survey and other promotional service providers;
•	Customer service vendors;
•	Web hosting and cloud service providers;
•	Data analytics suppliers;
•	Product experts and technology consultants; or
•	Legal compliance advisors.
•	Supply it to customer lead generation providers;
•	Interact with us at tradeshows and conferences;
•	Allow us to visit your business; or
• Provide it to us in the content of any communications you direct to New Pig.
•	Communicate with you regarding surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions;
•	Provide customer service; or
•	Verify customer information.
•	Product experts and technology consultants; or
•	Legal compliance advisors.
Demographic information such as your age, birthday, sex, gender, job title, role, other professional interests, your status as a military veteran, and any inferences we might draw from such information.
•	Create an account with us;
•	Participate in a promotion, contest or survey;
•	Submit a form on the Site; or
•	Provide it to us in the content of any communications you direct to New Pig.
•	Administer your account;
•	Communicate with you regarding surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions;
•	Provide customer service;
•	Analyze your consumer preferences; or
•	Contact you with information on new products, services, promotions and other updates in which we think you may be interested.
•	Survey and other promotional service providers;
•	Marketing vendors;
•	Web hosting and cloud service providers; or
•	Data analytics suppliers.
Credit/debit card or other payment/financial information.
•	Order and pay for any goods or services advertised on or through the Services.
•	Process or fulfill orders and transactions which you have authorized; or
•	Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, and prosecute those responsible for such activity.
•	Credit/debit card processors and other payment processing entities.
Account access information, including your password.
•	Create an account on the Site.
•	Administer your Site account;
•	Detect security incidents; or
•	Undertake activities to verify, maintain and improve the safety of the Site and the Services.
•	Web hosting and cloud service providers; or
•	Technology consultants
First-party cookie identifiers set directly by New Pig, which may include information on your interaction with the Site, any New Pig application, or any New Pig ad, and any inferences we might draw from such information.
•	Visit or use the Site, automatically.
•	Recognize you on return visits to the Site;
•	Analyze how you interact with our Site;
•	Identify products and services in which you might be interested;
•	Detect security incidents;
•	Undertake activities to verify, maintain and improve the quality or safety of the Site and Site-related services;
•	Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality with the Site;
•	Conduct data analysis and testing;
•	Undertake internal research for technological development and demonstration; or
•	Monitor Site usage.
•	Web hosting and cloud service providers; or
•	Data analytics suppliers.
Third-party cookie identifiers, internet protocol (IP) addresses, pixels and other online identifiers, browsing history, search history, email activity, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement, and any inferences we might draw from such information.
•	Visit or use the Site, automatically.
•	Monitor Site usage;
•	Count ad views or impressions, verify the positioning and quality of ad impressions;
•	Evaluate how you review and respond to emails we send you; or
•	Provide you with information on new products, services, promotions and other updates in which we think you may be interested.
•	Data analytics providers;
•	Marketing firms including email analytics vendors; or
•	Targeted advertising networks.
We may also use or disclose any of the above categories of Personal Information we collect for one or more of the following reasons:
• To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collections;
• As necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our customers or others;
• To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, subpoena, court order, other legal process or governmental regulations;
• As otherwise described to you at or before the point when we collect your Personal Information;
• To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by us is among the assets transferred.
This Site may use cross-device tracking technologies to try and connect your activity on the Site across the various devices you use to access and use the Site. You may be able to opt-out of such cross-device tracking by contacting us at privacy@newpig.com
By providing to New Pig the Personal Information and other data referenced above, you agree that we may use the Personal Information and other data in accordance with the terms of this Policy. We will not collect additional categories of Personal Information or use the Personal Information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.
^Top
Disclosure or Sale of Personal Information
Except as noted herein, New Pig does not sell or share your Personal Information with any person or entity outside of New Pig.
We may disclose certain portions of your Personal Information to analytics providers, advertising networks, and other service providers or third parties for certain business purposes as identified above, and receive something of value in exchange for this disclosure.
As referenced in the table of Personal Information we collect, use and share, the Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, analyze how visitors and customers interact with our Site, and for other purposes disclosed above. We may employ other companies to provide similar marketing services on our behalf. With our approval, these third parties may also place “cookies” for analysis purposes. These third-party companies will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose. We do not use cookies to store credit card information or other financial information. You are not required to accept cookies. However, certain functionality of the Site may not work properly (if at all) if you reject cookies.
Depending on where you reside, the disclosure of your cookie identifiers, including your IP address, in exchange for certain third-party services may be considered a sale of your Personal Information, and you may have the right to opt-out of any such sale of your Personal Information by New Pig.
This Site may use Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager, which are web analytics services that use cookies to analyze your use of our Site. The information collected by these cookies about your use of the Site (including your IP address) is transmitted to and stored on a Google server in the United States. Google uses this information to assess your use of the Site, providing reports on data such as how often you visit, what pages you view when you visit, and what other websites you have visited prior to visiting our Site. Google may transfer this information to third parties, if required by law or if third parties process the information on behalf of Google. View an overview of Google’s data privacy practices for Google Analytics at https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245. For more information on Google’s privacy practices generally, please review Google’s privacy policy at https://policies.google.com/privacy.To opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics, you may be able to download and install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
New Pig allows cookies, IP addresses and marketing information to be collected and managed by our third-party marketing vendors in order to provide you with targeted ads based on what you appear to be interested in as a result of your activity online, both on our Site and elsewhere. You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by us or on our behalf by clicking here.
If you opt-out, you will still see ads but they will not be personalized based on your online activity. Please note that if you disable your cookies or upgrade your browser after opting out, you will need to opt-out again. Further, if you use multiple browsers or devices you will need to execute this opt-out on each browser or device.
You can also generally opt-out of receiving targeted ads from third-party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) by visiting http://optout.networkadvertising.org/. You may opt-out of receiving targeted advertisements from other companies that perform interest-based advertising services, including some that we may work with, via the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) site at http://optout.aboutads.info/. Please note that when using the ad industry opt-out tools described above, you may need to execute opt-outs for each browser or device that you use, and that other companies’ opt-outs may function differently than our opt-out.
New Pig may also rent out its customer list to lead generation providers. New Pig’s customer list may include your name, company name, and physical address. This transfer of our customer list may cause you to receive information from third parties, who are not affiliated with New Pig, about third-party products or services in which you may be interested. You can opt-out of your information being shared in this way by using the contact details provided in the “Contacting New Pig Corporation” section below. You may also opt-out of this specific kind of sharing through your account settings, by selecting “Marketing Preferences” under “My Account” and using the choices available there.
Certain areas of the Site may integrate with social media sharing services which will let you share content from the Site with other online services. Your use of such features may enable the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the relevant social sharing service. Please review the privacy policies of those social media services for more information about how such services handle the information you provide to or share through them.
New Pig neither collects nor sells the Personal Information of minors under 16 years of age.
^Top
Your Rights and Choices
Depending on where you reside, you may have one or more of the following rights with regard to New Pig’s collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information:
• The right to request that we disclose what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose or sell about you;
• The right to request the deletion of Personal Information we have collected or maintain about you;
• The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information; and • The right not to receive discriminatory treatment by New Pig, in terms of the services and prices offered on or through our Services, because you exercised these rights regarding the collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information.
If you would like to access, review, edit, delete or have us properly dispose of any copies of the Personal Information that New Pig collected about you (subject to any applicable legal exceptions), if you would like to opt-out of receiving further information or limit what we share, or if you would like to exercise the above rights in any other way, please contact us at privacy@newpig.com or call us at 1-800-HOT-HOGS (1-800-468-4647).
You may be able to opt-out of New Pig sharing your Personal Information with the entities identified in this Policy by sending us an email at the address above, unless the sharing of your Personal Information is necessary to perform one of the following business purposes: to count ad impressions and evaluate their effectiveness; to detect, protect against, and prosecute security incidents; to debug or troubleshoot functional errors that may arise with the Services; to complete short-term tasks related to an existing interaction you have with New Pig; to maintain or service your account; to process payments and fulfill orders or other transactions you authorize; to verify your customer information; and to ensure the safety and quality of the Services.
New Pig will do its best to accommodate any request to delete or properly dispose of any copies of your Personal Information, but we cannot guarantee we can eliminate all Personal Information from the specified uses. Therefore, please be as specific as possible in any request to delete or dispose of copies of your Personal Information. We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:
1.	Complete the transaction for which we collected the Personal Information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise to perform a contract we entered into with you;
2.	Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities;
3.	Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
4.	Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law;
5.	Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546);
6.	Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent;
7.	Enable solely solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us;
8.	Comply with a legal obligation; or
9.	Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
If you choose to delete certain portions of your Personal Information, it may affect your ability to use certain New Pig Services. If the request relates to information that New Pig needs to make the Site or other Services function properly for you, you may no longer be able to use those Services. Any removal of content by New Pig does not ensure or guarantee complete or comprehensive removal of the content in all places. The content may have been shared or reposted by other parties, or federal or state law may require maintenance of the content or information.
You may grant an authorized agent written permission to submit requests regarding your Personal Information, but we may deny authorized agent requests absent proof that you authorized such agent to act on your behalf, or if we are unable to verify your identity.
New Pig is required to verify the identity of any person or entity that requests the disclosure or deletion of Personal Information. If you have a password-protected account with us, we will use our existing authentication procedures to verify your identity. For most other consumer requests, New Pig will ask you to provide information that matches at least two pieces of personal information we store about you before responding to your request. If you would like to request the specific pieces of your personal information that New Pig has collected, or if you would like us to delete highly sensitive information, you will need to match at least three pieces of information we store about you, and you must provide a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose personal information you are requesting.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you.
Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.
We will only use Personal Information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
New Pig reserves the right to maintain proper business records as required by law, or for otherwise legitimate business purposes to the extent permitted by law, even if such records contain portions of your Personal Information.
If you would like to opt-out of receiving promotional emails from New Pig, please follow the opt-out instructions at the bottom of the email or send New Pig a detailed email at privacy@newpig.com
Some browsers also have a ”do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked, and New Pig will attempt to treat such technical signals as valid opt-out requests for online tracking related to targeted advertising. To learn more about other ways to opt-out of certain kinds of targeted advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website and the Digital Advertising Alliance website. Options you select are browser- and device-specific.
^Top
Securing Personal Information
New Pig employs industry best practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your Personal Information such as firewalls and authentication protection. New Pig will periodically review its security policies and implement changes from time to time. However, we cannot and do not guarantee complete security, as it does not exist on the internet. While New Pig takes the issue of protecting your Personal Information seriously, you should exercise discretion in what information you disclose or transmit to the Site. If you are concerned about sending information to New Pig over the internet, please send the information by mail or call us to make other arrangements.
New Pig retains collected information for a reasonable amount of time in order to fulfill the stated purpose for why the information was collected. New Pig will also retain collected information connected to business records for periods of time required by law. If New Pig determines that collected information is no longer needed, it will delete such information. Our collection times will be consistent with applicable law.
^Top
Children's Privacy
New Pig’s Services are intended for individuals 18 years of age and older. Our Services are not directed at, marketed to, nor intended for, children under 16 years of age. New Pig does not knowingly collect or sell any information, including Personal Information, from children under 16 years of age. If New Pig learns that it has collected any information regarding a person younger than 16 years of age, New Pig will delete or destroy the information immediately.
If there is concern that information regarding a person younger than 16 years of age was somehow collected by New Pig, any minor, or the parent(s) or legal guardian(s) of such minor, who wishes to request the removal of the minor’s information should submit their request by using the contact details provided in the “Contacting New Pig Corporation” section below.
^Top
Non-U.S. Concerns
The Services are meant for individuals within the United States. New Pig only knowingly collects information from individuals within the United States. If you provide information to New Pig from outside of the United States, you do so at your own risk. If you are outside of the United States, you are responsible for complying with any local laws regarding use of the Services, and related data collection. You also agree and acknowledge that by providing any information, including Personal Information, through the Services, that such information will be transmitted to, and stored in, the United States.
^Top
Terms of Use
The Terms of Use for the Site is incorporated by reference into this Policy. The Terms of Use can be found at:
https://www.newpig.com/termsofuse.
^Top
Contacting New Pig Corporation
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, the Services, or your dealings with New Pig, you can contact:
Web Services Manager
New Pig Corporation
One Pork Avenue
P.O. Box 304
Tipton, PA 16684 USA
Email: privacy@newpig.com
Phone: 1-800-HOT-HOGS (1-800-468-4647)
Fax: 1-800-621-PIGS® (1-800-621-7447)
New Pig intends to strictly enforce this Policy. If you believe there has been some violation of this Policy, please contact New Pig.
This Policy was last updated on December 18, 2019.
Featured Products
Get your very ownPigalog Buying Guide!Mail It To MeView Online
Today’s Daily Deal
Daily Deal - Limit 1
KIT220
(5)
PIG® Spill Kit in High-Visibility Bag
Absorbs up to 9 gal.
Absorbs Oils, Coolants, Solvents, Water – Universal
Was $135.00 - $162.00
Now $137.70
Sign up for PIG Deals
Score incredible offers!
Sign Up
Please enter a valid email
You’re signed up!
Keep an eye out for exclusive promos served straight to your inbox.
Customer Service
Contact Us
PIG Promise
Returns
Shipping & Terms
Federal Shipping & Ordering
Federal Overseas Shipping
Discount Programs
ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES
BEST SERVICE AROUND We’re obsessed with keeping you happy! Leak and spill experts
are standing by with free advice to get you unstumped. Learn more.
The New Pig No Guff Guarantee® We stand behind 100% of our products 100% of the time. If you’re not happy, we’ll refund every penny, including taxes and shipping both ways. Zero risk. No guff. All good.
One Pork Avenue • PO Box 304 • Tipton, PA 16684-0304 1-855-493-HOGS (493-4647) • Fax: 1-800-621-PIGS (621-7447) • hothogs@newpig.com
© 2020 New Pig Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
Score incredible offers!
Sign Up
Please enter a valid email
You’re signed up!
Keep an eye out for exclusive promos served straight to your inbox.
Talk to a LEAK & SPILL expert
Our team in Tipton, PA is here to help.
Forgot password?
Reset
First time here? Register now.
Know your item #? Order faster!
Please enter an item number.
Personal Safety (PPE)
EPA's SPCC: Active vs. Passive Containment for Oil Spill Prevention
EPA's Resource Conservation & Recovery Act (RCRA) Waste Management Program
EPA's Stormwater Pollution Prevention Plan (SWPPP) Requirements
EPA's Closed Container & Secondary Containment for Haz Waste
